Has Ian sold his house yet?
伊恩已把他的房子卖掉了吗?
Yes, he has.
是的,卖掉了.
He sold it last week.
他上星期卖掉的.
Has he moved to his new house yet?
他已经搬进新居了吗?
No, not yet.
不,还没有.
He's still here.
他仍在这里.
He's going to move tomorrow.
他打算明天搬家.
When? Tomorrow morning?
什么时候?明天上午吗?
No. Tomorrow afternoon.
不,明天下午.
I'll miss him.
我会想念他的.
He has always been a good neighbour.
他一直是个好邻居.
He's a very nice person.
他是个非常好的人,
We'll all miss him.
我们大家都会想念他的.
When will the new people move into this house?
新住户什么时候搬进这所房子?
I think that they'll move in the day after tomorrow.
我想他们将在后天搬进来吧.
Will you see Ian today, Jenny?
詹尼,你今天会见到伊恩吗?
Yes, I will.
是的,我会见到他.
Please give him my regards.
请代我问候他.
Poor Ian!
可怜的伊恩!
He didn't want to leave this house.
他本不想离开这幢房子.
No, he didn't want to leave. but his wife did!
是啊,他是不想离开,可是他妻子要离开.